Oh, my God.
I know.
Monica's going
to have a baby.
Hey, can this count
as her "something new"?
Oh, my God.
Hey, do you think this is why
Chandler took off?
No, she had to have
just taken that test
because I took out the trash
last night.
Oh, God, this is turning
into the worst wedding day ever.
The bride is pregnant,
the groom is missing
and I'm still
holding this.
Okay, Phoebe, we cannot
tell anyone about this.
Okay?
Right. Yeah, okay.
Hey, wait.
Do you know what kind
of birth control
she was using?
No. Why?
Just for the future.
This is hardly
a commercial for it.
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Anything?
No. I talked to Joey
on the set.
He hasn't heard
from him.
I talked to Chandler's
parents again.
You told them
he was missing?
No. I made it seem like
I was just calling to chat.
I'm pretty sure
they both think
I'm interested in them.
All right, we've
got to tell her
that he's gone.
No, hey, hey, we can't.
She's going to start
getting ready soon.
Can't you at least
stall her a little?
I'll go back to some
of the places I went last night.
Well, how much
time do you need?
How much time before
she absolutely has
to start getting ready?
One hour.
Give me two.
Then why do you ask?
Okay, wish me luck.
Okay. I'm going
with you.
Why?
Ross, you're tired.
You've been
looking all night
and clearly,
you suck at this.
I'll see
you guys later.
Do you know how
you're going to stall her?
I'll figure something out.
All right, good luck.
Hey.
Okay, so I thought
we'd start
with my makeup
and then do my hair.
Okay, uh, but before
you do that
I-I need you
to talk to me.
About what?
Um...
( voice breaking ):
I'm never going
to get married.
Yeah, you will.
The right guy's just
around the corner.
Okay, are we done with that?
No, Monica,
I'm serious.
Oh, maybe I should just
forget about it.
Become a lesbian
or something.
Any woman would be
lucky to have you.
Well, maybe it would
make me feel better
if I slept with Joey.
Rachel, are you okay?
Excuse me, Aaron?
Hi. Um...
I have a little problem
with the schedule.
See, originally, I wasn't
supposed to work today
and I have this wedding
that I really have to be at.
It's my best friend's
and I'm officiating
so I really can't
work past 4:00.
Joey, you've
got to stay
until the end.
We can't stop filming
just for you.
It's not like
it's your wedding.
I'm having surgery.
What?
Yeah, I just made up
the stuff about the wedding
because I didn't want
you to worry about me.
But I'm having
surgery today.
What kind of surgery?
Transplant.
But you're supposed
to work on Monday.
Hair transplant.
But you're not bald.
It's not on my head.
Look, Joey, there's
nothing I can do.
Besides, you're
probably going to be
out by 4:00 anyway.
We've just got
one short scene.
It's just you
and Richard
and God knows
he's a pro.
You'll be fine.
Morning, Richard.
Hey, you're here.
Great, great, great.
Let's get going, buddy.
We've got a scene
to shoot.
I'm wearing two belts.
Are you drunk?
No.
Yes, you are.
All right.
So this is your office.
How did you guys
find me?
I knew I should have
hid at the gym.
What the hell
are you doing?
Panicking...
and using the Internet
to try to prove
that I'm related to Monica.
How is she?
ROSS:
She's fine.
She doesn't know
you're gone.
And she doesn't
have to know, okay?
Now come on,
we're going home.
No, no, I can't do that.
Why not?
Because if I go home
we're going to become the Bings.
I can't be the Bings.
What's wrong with
being the Bings?
The Bings have
horrible marriages.
They yell, they fight
and they use the pool boy
as a pawn in their sexual games.
Chandler, have
you ever put on a
black cocktail dress
and asked me up
to your hotel room?
No.
Then you are neither
of your parents.
It's not just
their marriage.
I mean, look at yours.
Look at everybody's.
The only person
that can make
marriage work
is Paul Newman.
And I have met me--
I am no Paul Newman.
I don't race cars,
I don't make popcorn.
None of my proceeds
go to charity.
But look, Chandler
right now, no one has
a lower opinion
of you than I do.
But I totally believe
you can do this.
I want to.
I love her so much.
But I'm afra...
This is too huge.
You know, okay,
you're right
it is huge.
So why don't we take
it just a little
bit at a time.
Okay, forget
getting married
for a second.
Just forget about it.
Can you just come home
and take a shower?
That's not
scary, right?
Depends on what you mean
by "we."
Okay.
The nights
are the hardest.
But then the day comes
and that's every bit
as hard as the night.
And then the night comes again.
The days and nights are hard,
I get it, okay?
Look, Rachel, I'm sorry.
I have to start getting ready.
I'm getting married today.
I know.
At dusk.
That's such a hard time for me.
Okay.
I'm going to go
put my makeup on.
We have to be at the
hotel in an hour.
Okay. Wait.
What?
Let's go to lunch.
I can't go to lunch!
Right.
Oh, good God, I've fallen down!
What's going on?
Okay.
All right, honey, listen.
When I tell you what
I'm about to tell you
I need you to remember
that we are all here for you
and that we love you.
Okay, you're really
freaking me out.
We can't find Chandler.
...s vest.
We can't find Chandler's vest.
How can that be?
Wait, are you serious?
Found the vest.
I mean, we're going to have
to keep an eye on it.
You know, make sure
we don't lose it again.
Oh.
Oh, well, okay.
Don't scare me like that, okay?
I mean, for
a minute there
I was like, Oh, my God,
the worst has happened.
Oh, whoo!
So-so, you two
were married, huh?
What happened,
you just drift apart?
Here comes the bride.
Oh.
( gasps )
Oh, my God, Monica!
( gasping )
I want to wear
this every day.
You look so beautiful.
I'm so happy for me.
( phone rings )
Hello.
Hey. Did Chandler show up yet?
Yeah. We got him back;
everything's fine.
Damn it!
What? Why? Where are you?
I'm still on the set.
Joey, the wedding is
in less than an hour.
I know. I'm sorry.
The guy's drunk.
They won't let me go
until we get this.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to have to find
another minister.
No! No, I'm the minister.
All right, look, look,
put them both on the phone.
I'll marry them right now.
Oh! Joey, I have to go.
Hey, don't you hang up on me.
I'll marry you and me
right now-- I have the power.
There you go.
You put on a tuxedo.
Now, that wasn't
so scary, was it?
No.
I'm telling you, just
a little bit at a time.
Yeah, okay, wh-what's
the next little bit?
Getting married.
( gasps )
Okay, okay,
but you can...
you can do that, too.
just like you've
done everything else.
Yeah, you're right.
I... I-I can do that.
Yeah.
Okay, excuse me
for a minute.
Where... where are you going?
Ross, I'm not going
to run away again.
I just want to get
a little fresh air.
Okay.
Oh, fresh air.
RACHEL:
Okay, Phoebe, you're going
to have to cover for me.
PHOEBE:
Wait. Maybe, maybe
you're overreacting.
You do that, you know?
Oh. Well, Phoebe,
we got to do something.
You know? I mean,
there's no way
Joey's going to
make it in time
so I'm going to go
through the hotel
and see if there's any
other weddings going on.
Okay. Oh, but don't tell them
Monica's pregnant
'cause they frown on that.
Okay.
"Anastassakis
Papasifakis wedding."
Excellent.
Congratulations.
Mazel tov.
Hi. Oh, great hat.
Come here.
Listen, I need you to
perform another wedding.
Can you do that?
I don't know.
Are they Greek Orthodox?
Yeah, yeah, they're...
They're my friends, uh,
Monica Stephanopolous
and, uh... and
Chandler... Acidophilus.
Hi.
Has, um, anyone
seen Chandler?
I thought he
was with you.
He was with me.
Um, we're playing a little game;
you know, hide-and-seek.
You can't ask us, son.
That's cheating.
You're right.
Thanks for keeping me honest,
Dad.
Well, he better not
come by here.
He can't see the bride
in her wedding dress.
As I recall,
when we got married
I saw the groom
in the wedding dress.
That was after the wedding.
It's not bad luck then.
Honey, it isn't good luck.
Oh, my God!
Monica!
I know.
Hey, how's Chandler doing?
Great.
He's doing great.
Don't you worry
about Chandler.
Uh, Phoebe, can I
see you for a second?
Yeah.
What's going on?
Chandler's gone again.
Oh, my God!
Why would you play
hide-and-seek with someone
you know is a flight risk?
Aaron, you got
to let me go.
The guy's hammered.
I'm sorry, Joey.
As long as he's here
and he's conscious
we're still shooting.
You wouldn't happen to have
a very big fork?
So I, uh, I just
talked to the director.
That's it.
We're done for the day.
Have we finished the scene?
Yeah, you were wonderful.
As were you.
So I got your car.
It's right outside.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
No, no, no,
we got to go.
Come on.
Here we go.
Is that my ass?
There he is!
What?
Hey, no!
You're not getting away
this time, mister
unless you want that ass-kicking
we talked about!
Ross!
Hi-ya!
I'm serious.
You're not walking out
on my sister.
That's right; I'm not.
Then where the hell
have you been?
I know about Monica.
You know?
What?
I heard you
and Rachel talking.
What, what,
talking about what?
You don't know?
If someone doesn't tell me
what's going on right now...
What, you'll "hi-ya"?
Monica's pregnant.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
And you're not...
you're not freaking out?
Well, I was.
Then I went down
to the gift shop
'cause I was out of cigarettes.
Cigarettes?!
Big picture, please.
So when I was
in the gift shop
that's when I, uh...
saw this.
And I thought
anything that can fit into this
can't be scary.
You obviously didn't see
Chucky III.
No, but come on.
Look how cute and small this is.
So I got it to give Monica
so she'd... know I was okay.
Dude.
Way to go, son.
I knew you'd find him.
Our little boy
is getting married.
Oh, look at you.
So handsome.
You look beautiful, Mom.
( clears throat )
You look beautiful, too, Dad.
I love you both.
I'm so glad you're here.
Are you Chandler?
Are you Joey?
Huh, this is nice.
What?
I've never walked down the aisle
knowing it can't end in divorce.
( sighs )
I wish your grandmother
had lived to see this.
She's right there.
Not that
old crone.
My mother.
Congratulations,
darling.
We love you,
sweetheart.
You look beautiful.
Is this new?
Not now.
Okay.
Who is this?
I am Father Karamessos.
He's Greek Orthodox.
As are you.
Let us begin.
Dearly beloved...
That's my line.
I can take it
from here, thanks.
Dearly beloved,
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
You may be confused by this now
but you won't be
Memorial Day weekend, 2002.
Well, let's get started before
the groom takes off again, huh?
We are gathered here today
to join this man and this woman
in the bonds of holy matrimony.
I've known Monica and Chandler
for a long time
and I cannot imagine two people
more perfect for each other.
And now...
as I've left my notes
in my dressing room
we shall proceed to the vows.
Monica.
He took off?
Go on, go on.
Chandler, for so long, I...
I wondered if I would
ever find my prince.
My soul mate.
Then three years ago,
at another wedding
I turned to a friend
for comfort
and instead
I found everything that I'd
ever been looking for
my whole life.
And now, here we are,
with our future before us...
and I only want to
spend it with you.
My prince, my soul mate,
my friend.
Unless you don't want to.
You go.
Chandler.
Uh, that's okay.
Monica, I thought this
was going to be
the most difficult thing
I ever had to do.
But when I saw you
walking down that aisle
I realized how
simple it was.
I love you.
Any surprises that
come our way
it's okay, because
I will always love you.
You are the person
I was meant to spend
the rest of my life with.
You want to know
if I'm sure?
You may now
kiss the bride.
So...
I guess by the powers
vested in me
by the state of New York
and the Internet guys...
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Oh, wait.
Do you take each other?
I do.
Yeah, you do.
Rings.
Oh, crap. Okay, um...
Let's do the rings.
We good?
Okay.
Once again, I pronounce you
husband and wife.
Kiss her again.
I love you.
And I know about the baby.
What baby?
Our baby.
We have a baby?
Phoebe found your pregnancy test
in the trash.
I didn't take
a pregnancy test.
Then who did?
Look at them.
Oh, and they're
going to have a baby.
Uh-huh.